Guide to the Peter Palmquist Cased Photographs Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Additions from Other Collections, Series VII
  - Daguerreotypes
    - Daguerreotype unmounted sixth plate of an indistinct studio portrait of a man, undated (Box 55)
    - Daguerreotype unmounted sixth plate with no extant image, undated (Box 55)
    - Daguerreotype unmounted quarter plate of a studio portrait of a woman and a tintype copy photograph, undated (Box 55)
  - Ambrotype unmounted sixth plate with an indistinct image of a boy and two girls, undated (Box 55)
  - Ambrotype package liner remnant, quarter plate (Box 55)
  - Advertising
    - Hendley, F., Advertising card, Cheltenham, England, circa 1865 (Box 55)
    - Unidentified manufacturer, Union case advertsiement sheet, sixth plate, circa 1855 (Box 55)
  - Cased Photograph Components
    - Case pads, ninth plate, 2 (Box 55)
    - Case pads, sixth plate, 4 (Box 55)
    - Mats, ninth plate, 12 (Box 55)
    - Mats, sixth plate, 29 (Box 55)
    - Mats, quarter plate, 4 (Box 55)
    - Mat, half plate (Box 55)
    - Preservers, sixth plate to half plate, 10 (Box 56)
    - Case Covers, sixth plate to half plate, 38 (Box 56)